<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Weston Bishop</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Weston Bishop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:17:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fueling the Hybrid Athlete: The Power of a Low GL Diet for Lean Muscle and Peak Performance</title>
      <link>/posts/lgl-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:17:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/lgl-diet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the fitness space there is no shortage of diet fads promising ripped physiques and explosive performance. The internet is littered with dietary dogmas such as the so-called &amp;ldquo;animal based&amp;rdquo; diet and many others. These fad diets typically have something to offer, but if one focuses on metabolic science, one principle stands out: controlling glycemic load (GL) has the power to unlock &lt;em&gt;lean muscle growth, sustained energy, and metabolic health&lt;/em&gt;. For the hybrid athlete who trains for both strength and endurance, a low GL diet is the foundation for optimal athletic performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;image-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;/images/baby.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Baby Weston&#34; /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;Hi, I&#39;m &lt;b&gt;Weston Bishop&lt;/b&gt;, a passionate developer dedicated to building impactful software solutions. I specialize in &lt;i&gt;web development, Android applications, and software engineering&lt;/i&gt;. With a focus on simplicity and efficient functionality, I strive to create projects that are both elegant and practical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;Outside of coding, I am deeply intereted in &lt;i&gt;fitness and the journey of the soul&lt;/i&gt;. My journey is driven by continuous learning and the pursuit of mastery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are school or personal projects that I’ve done recently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;stock-tracker&#34;&gt;Stock Tracker&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stock tracker is a stock market simulator, visualizer, and strategy backtester using Python, Pandas, and Matplotlib. It uses the Yahoo Finance API to grab historical stock data, which the user can visualize over a timeframe with various indicators. The user may also backtest the portfolio with the market simulator, simulating trading costs and drawdown, using conditions involving metrics like RSI, MACD, and Bollinger Bands. In the future, I plan to add a more user-friendly interface, and ML / optimization functions to pick stocks and optimize trading conditions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
